<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="102122" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="[KS] Chinese Brick Relief" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Give your city a cultural glow-up with authentic Chinese brick relief decals—perfect with China Packs!" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
### 🚨 PLEASE READ THE USAGE | KNOWN LIMITATIONS SECTIONS 🚨
 
👷🏻 Want to bring traditional Chinese architecture to life? This pack is for you!
 
### 🎨 About the Pack
The Chinese Brick Relief Decal Pack brings a touch of history and culture to Cities: Skylines II! Inspired by intricate brick carvings found in ancient temples, courtyards, and historic streets, these high-quality decals allow you to create authentic Chinese-inspired builds.
 
Whether you're building a traditional village, an ancient city wall, a temple complex, or adding cultural charm to modern structures, these detailed relief patterns will elevate your designs.
 
### 📦 Contents of the Pack
✅ 20+ high-resolution brick relief decals with authentic carvings
✅ Various designs, including floral motifs, mythological creatures, geometric patterns, and calligraphy
✅ Ideal for temples, historic streets, courtyards, gates and walls
✅ Located in the “DECALS” tab for easy access
 
### 🔨 Usage
🛠️ Recommended mods for best results: Move It, Extra Decals Tool, Procedural Objects, and Adaptive Networks
🖌️ Apply decals to walls, floors, and other surfaces to recreate a historical look
🏗️ Mix and match with other assets to blend tradition into modern designs
 
### 🛑 Known Limitations
🚧 Some decals may slightly overlap textures due to the game's layering system
🏗️ Decals may not conform perfectly to curved or sloped surfaces
🎨 Color variations may differ depending on your graphics settings
 
### 🌐 Localization
- English
- Chinese Simplified
- Chinese Traditional
 
💡 Want to take your city to the next level? Try combining these decals with traditional Chinese architecture assets for a truly immersive experience!
 
### 💬 Questions? Need help? Drop a comment!

If you're reading this, you just unlocked the achievement "Architect of Tradition" 🏯. Congratulations! 🎉
 
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot01.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot02.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot03.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot04.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot05.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.2.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="80529" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Add Chinese Feng Shui" />
	<!--ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog-->
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon, buymeacoffee, kofi, crowdin, gitlab-->
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/XE5nBYskcd" />
</Publish>
